Journals
--------

[Topics
------](https://www.mdpi.com/topics)

Information
-----------

[Editing Services
----------------](https://www.mdpi.com/authors/english)

Initiatives
-----------

About
-----

Notice
------

You can make submissions to other journals [here](https://susy.mdpi.com/user/manuscripts/upload).

_clear_

Notice
------

You are accessing a machine-readable page. In order to be human-readable, please install an RSS reader.

Continue Cancel

_clear_

All articles published by MDPI are made immediately available worldwide under an open access license. No special permission is required to reuse all or part of the article published by MDPI, including figures and tables. For articles published under an open access Creative Common CC BY license, any part of the article may be reused without permission provided that the original article is clearly cited. For more information, please refer to [https://www.mdpi.com/openaccess](https://www.mdpi.com/openaccess).

Feature papers represent the most advanced research with significant potential for high impact in the field. A Feature Paper should be a substantial original Article that involves several techniques or approaches, provides an outlook for future research directions and describes possible research applications.

Feature papers are submitted upon individual invitation or recommendation by the scientific editors and must receive positive feedback from the reviewers.

Editor’s Choice articles are based on recommendations by the scientific editors of MDPI journals from around the world. Editors select a small number of articles recently published in the journal that they believe will be particularly interesting to readers, or important in the respective research area. The aim is to provide a snapshot of some of the most exciting work published in the various research areas of the journal.

Original Submission Date Received: .

You seem to have javascript disabled. Please note that many of the page functionalities won't work as expected without javascript enabled.

Search for Articles:

Title / Keyword

Author / Affiliation / Email

Journal

All Journals Acoustics Acta Microbiologica Hellenica (AMH) Actuators Administrative Sciences Adolescents Advances in Respiratory Medicine (ARM) Aerobiology Aerospace Agriculture AgriEngineering Agrochemicals Agronomy AI Air Algorithms Allergies Alloys Analytica Analytics Anatomia Anesthesia Research Animals Antibiotics Antibodies Antioxidants Applied Biosciences Applied Mechanics Applied Microbiology Applied Nano Applied Sciences Applied System Innovation (ASI) AppliedChem AppliedMath Aquaculture Journal Architecture Arthropoda Arts Astronomy Atmosphere Atoms Audiology Research Automation Axioms Bacteria Batteries Behavioral Sciences Beverages Big Data and Cognitive Computing (BDCC) BioChem Bioengineering Biologics Biology Biology and Life Sciences Forum Biomass Biomechanics BioMed Biomedicines BioMedInformatics Biomimetics Biomolecules Biophysica Biosensors BioTech Birds Blockchains Brain Sciences Buildings Businesses C Cancers Cardiogenetics Catalysts Cells Ceramics Challenges ChemEngineering Chemistry Chemistry Proceedings Chemosensors Children Chips CivilEng Clean Technologies (Clean Technol.) Climate Clinical and Translational Neuroscience (CTN) Clinical Bioenergetics Clinics and Practice Clocks & Sleep Coasts Coatings Colloids and Interfaces Colorants Commodities Complications Compounds Computation Computer Sciences & Mathematics Forum Computers Condensed Matter Conservation Construction Materials Corrosion and Materials Degradation (CMD) Cosmetics COVID Crops Cryo Cryptography Crystals Current Issues in Molecular Biology (CIMB) Current Oncology Dairy Data Dentistry Journal Dermato Dermatopathology Designs Diabetology Diagnostics Dietetics Digital Disabilities Diseases Diversity DNA Drones Drugs and Drug Candidates (DDC) Dynamics Earth Ecologies Econometrics Economies Education Sciences Electricity Electrochem Electronic Materials Electronics Emergency Care and Medicine Encyclopedia Endocrines Energies Energy Storage and Applications (ESA) Eng Engineering Proceedings Entropy Environmental and Earth Sciences Proceedings Environments Epidemiologia Epigenomes European Burn Journal (EBJ) European Journal of Investigation in Health, Psychology and Education (EJIHPE) Fermentation Fibers FinTech Fire Fishes Fluids Foods Forecasting Forensic Sciences Forests Fossil Studies Foundations Fractal and Fractional (Fractal Fract) Fuels Future Future Internet Future Pharmacology Future Transportation Galaxies Games Gases Gastroenterology Insights Gastrointestinal Disorders Gastronomy Gels Genealogy Genes Geographies GeoHazards Geomatics Geometry Geosciences Geotechnics Geriatrics Glacies Gout, Urate, and Crystal Deposition Disease (GUCDD) Grasses Hardware Healthcare Hearts Hemato Hematology Reports Heritage Histories Horticulturae Hospitals Humanities Humans Hydrobiology Hydrogen Hydrology Hygiene Immuno Infectious Disease Reports Informatics Information Infrastructures Inorganics Insects Instruments Intelligent Infrastructure and Construction International Journal of Environmental Research and Public Health (IJERPH) International Journal of Financial Studies (IJFS) International Journal of Molecular Sciences (IJMS) International Journal of Neonatal Screening (IJNS) International Journal of Plant Biology (IJPB) International Journal of Topology International Journal of Translational Medicine (IJTM) International Journal of Turbomachinery, Propulsion and Power (IJTPP) International Medical Education (IME) Inventions IoT ISPRS International Journal of Geo-Information (IJGI) J Journal of Ageing and Longevity (JAL) Journal of Cardiovascular Development and Disease (JCDD) Journal of Clinical & Translational Ophthalmology (JCTO) Journal of Clinical Medicine (JCM) Journal of Composites Science (J. Compos. Sci.) Journal of Cybersecurity and Privacy (JCP) Journal of Dementia and Alzheimer's Disease (JDAD) Journal of Developmental Biology (JDB) Journal of Experimental and Theoretical Analyses (JETA) Journal of Functional Biomaterials (JFB) Journal of Functional Morphology and Kinesiology (JFMK) Journal of Fungi (JoF) Journal of Imaging (J. Imaging) Journal of Intelligence (J. Intell.) Journal of Low Power Electronics and Applications (JLPEA) Journal of Manufacturing and Materials Processing (JMMP) Journal of Marine Science and Engineering (JMSE) Journal of Market Access & Health Policy (JMAHP) Journal of Molecular Pathology (JMP) Journal of Nanotheranostics (JNT) Journal of Nuclear Engineering (JNE) Journal of Otorhinolaryngology, Hearing and Balance Medicine (JOHBM) Journal of Parks Journal of Personalized Medicine (JPM) Journal of Pharmaceutical and BioTech Industry (JPBI) Journal of Respiration (JoR) Journal of Risk and Financial Management (JRFM) Journal of Sensor and Actuator Networks (JSAN) Journal of the Oman Medical Association (JOMA) Journal of Theoretical and Applied Electronic Commerce Research (JTAER) Journal of Vascular Diseases (JVD) Journal of Xenobiotics (JoX) Journal of Zoological and Botanical Gardens (JZBG) Journalism and Media Kidney and Dialysis Kinases and Phosphatases Knowledge LabMed Laboratories Land Languages Laws Life Limnological Review Lipidology Liquids Literature Livers Logics Logistics Lubricants Lymphatics Machine Learning and Knowledge Extraction (MAKE) Machines Macromol Magnetism Magnetochemistry Marine Drugs Materials Materials Proceedings Mathematical and Computational Applications (MCA) Mathematics Medical Sciences Medical Sciences Forum Medicina Medicines Membranes Merits Metabolites Metals Meteorology Methane Methods and Protocols (MPs) Metrics Metrology Micro Microbiology Research Micromachines Microorganisms Microplastics Minerals Mining Modelling Modern Mathematical Physics Molbank Molecules Multimodal Technologies and Interaction (MTI) Muscles Nanoenergy Advances Nanomanufacturing Nanomaterials NDT Network Neuroglia Neurology International NeuroSci Nitrogen Non-Coding RNA (ncRNA) Nursing Reports Nutraceuticals Nutrients Obesities Oceans Onco Optics Oral Organics Organoids Osteology Oxygen Parasitologia Particles Pathogens Pathophysiology Pediatric Reports Pets Pharmaceuticals Pharmaceutics Pharmacoepidemiology Pharmacy Philosophies Photochem Photonics Phycology Physchem Physical Sciences Forum Physics Physiologia Plants Plasma Platforms Pollutants Polymers Polysaccharides Populations Poultry Powders Proceedings Processes Prosthesis Proteomes Psychiatry International Psychoactives Psychology International Publications Quantum Beam Science (QuBS) Quantum Reports Quaternary Radiation Reactions Real Estate Receptors Recycling Regional Science and Environmental Economics (RSEE) Religions Remote Sensing Reports Reproductive Medicine (Reprod. Med.) Resources Rheumato Risks Robotics Ruminants Safety Sci Scientia Pharmaceutica (Sci. Pharm.) Sclerosis Seeds Sensors Separations Sexes Signals Sinusitis Smart Cities Social Sciences Société Internationale d’Urologie Journal (SIUJ) Societies Software Soil Systems Solar Solids Spectroscopy Journal Sports Standards Stats Stresses Surfaces Surgeries Surgical Techniques Development Sustainability Sustainable Chemistry Symmetry SynBio Systems Targets Taxonomy Technologies Telecom Textiles Thalassemia Reports Therapeutics Thermo Time and Space Tomography Tourism and Hospitality Toxics Toxins Transplantology Trauma Care Trends in Higher Education Tropical Medicine and Infectious Disease (TropicalMed) Universe Urban Science Uro Vaccines Vehicles Venereology Veterinary Sciences Vibration Virtual Worlds Viruses Vision Waste Water Wild Wind Women World World Electric Vehicle Journal (WEVJ) Youth Zoonotic Diseases

Article Type

All Article Types Article Review Communication Editorial Abstract Book Review Brief Communication Brief Report Case Report Clinicopathological Challenge Comment Commentary Concept Paper Conference Report Correction Creative Data Descriptor Discussion Entry Essay Expression of Concern Extended Abstract Field Guide Guidelines Hypothesis Interesting Images Letter New Book Received Obituary Opinion Perspective Proceeding Paper Project Report Protocol Registered Report Reply Retraction Short Note Study Protocol Systematic Review Technical Note Tutorial Viewpoint

Section

Special Issue

Volume

Issue

Number

Page

Logical OperatorOperator

AND OR

Search Text

Search Type

All fields Title Abstract Keywords Authors Affiliations Doi Full Text References

_add\_circle\_outline_

_remove\_circle\_outline_

Legal Information
-----------------

Need Help?
----------

### Support

Find support for a specific problem in the support section of our website.

### Feedback

Please let us know what you think of our products and services.

### Information

Visit our dedicated information section to learn more about MDPI.

_clear_

MDPI Privacy Policy
===================

We have aligned this Privacy Policy with both the Swiss Data Protection Act (“SDPA”) and the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). The GDPR has established itself worldwide as a benchmark for strong data protection, therefore our company has set itself to implement the highest standards in data protection. As GDPR and SDPA may have slight differences in the definitions used, we base the following Privacy Policy text on GDPR definitions, which have the same meaning in SDPA. Notwithstanding the above, please note that whether and to what extent the GDPR or SDPA is applicable to you depends on the individual case.

1

**Scope**  

1.1

This website is made available by MDPI AG, Grosspeteranlage 5, 4052 Basel, Switzerland (“MDPI”) as the controller within the meaning of Art. 4 of the GDPR. MDPI is an open access publisher and provides platforms for open scientific exchange. The following privacy policy applies to the use of the website www.mdpi.com and the services offered via it including, but not limited to, Sciforum, Preprints, Scilit, Encylcopedia, WSForum and MDPI’s Submission System, “SuSy” and MDPI Books. In the event of any data protection related inquiry, you can contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.mdpi.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or you can reach our data protection officer Mr. Simon Brandmeier at [\[email protected\]](https://www.mdpi.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

1.2

This privacy policy informs you in accordance with Art. 12 ff. GDPR about how we handle your personal data when you use our website. In particular, it explains which data we collect and what we use it for. It also informs you about how and for what purpose this is done.

1.3

The protection of your personal data is important to us, especially with regard to safeguarding your personal rights when processing and using this information. When you use this website, various personal data are processed depending on the type and scope of use. Personal data is information that relates to an identified or identifiable natural person (hereinafter “data subject”); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified directly or indirectly (e.g. by means of association with an online identifier). This includes information such as the name, address, email, telephone number and date of birth.

2

**Automated data collection and processing by the browser**  

2.1

As with any website, our server automatically and temporarily collects information in the server log files that are transmitted by the browser while you are browsing through our website. Depending on the settings of your browser the following data are collected:

* IP address of the requesting computer
* the Internet page from which you visit us (referrer URL),
* Date, time and duration of the server session
* Browser type and version
* Type of end device and operating system used by the requesting computer

2.2

The storage of server log files is necessary for technical reasons to provide a functional website and to ensure system security. This also applies to the storage of your IP address, which is necessary and, under further conditions, can at least theoretically enable an assignment to your person. In addition to the above-mentioned purposes, we use server log files solely for the purpose of designing and optimizing our website in line with demand, purely for statistical purposes and without any reference to your person. A personal evaluation of the server log files does not take place. This data is not merged with other data sources. The access data collected in connection with the use of our website is only stored for the period of time for which this data is required to achieve the aforementioned purposes. Your IP address is stored on our web server for a maximum of two years for IT security purposes. For data which are stored through cookies, please see section 3 below.

2.3

If you visit our website to find out about or use our range of products and services, the basis for the temporary storage and processing of the server log files is Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b GDPR (legal basis), which permits the processing of data for the fulfilment of a contract or for the execution of pre-contractual measures. In addition, Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. f GDPR serves as the legal basis for the temporary storage of technical access data. Our legitimate interest in this regard is to be able to provide you with a technically functioning and user-friendly website and to ensure the security of our systems.

3

**Cookies and tracking tools used on our website**  

3.1

This website uses cookies and other tracking technologies. Cookies are small text files that contain an identification number. Cookies are stored on your computer, tablet or smartphone (“device”) when you call up our website. If you call up our website again, your device can be recognised on the basis of this identification number.

3.2

When you visit our website for the first time you will be asked whether you wish to give your consent, that cookies that collect personal data may be set. You can give your consent for all cookies (button “Allow all”), select the cookie categories (Preferences, Statistics, Marketing) you want to accept and select the “Allow selection” button or by clicking on the “Show details” button to make more user-defined settings. There you can decide by activating or by setting a check mark whether you give your consent for certain services or for certain categories of services or refuse consent for certain services. Consent is voluntary and you can revoke it at any time by clicking on the Cookiebot icon in the left corner at the bottom of our website (so-called footer) with effect for the future.

3.3

Cookies

3.3.1

Categories of cookies

Depending on the function and purpose of the data processing taking place, we categorise the cookies used on our website into the following three categories:

3.3.1.1

Necessary

These cookies are necessary to provide you with website functions and to fulfil our legal obligations. The legal basis for the processing of your personal data is our legitimate interest (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR) to make our website usable for you and to fulfil our legal obligations (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. c GDPR).

3.3.1.2

Statistics

We use these cookies for statistical analysis purposes to statistically record the use of our website. Statistics cookies help us to improve our website and to offer you content that is of particular relevance to you. The legal basis for the processing of your personal data is your consent pursuant to Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR, which you can give via our cookie banner. Your consent is always voluntary and is not required for the use of the website itself.

3.3.1.3

Marketing

We use these cookies for marketing purposes, for example to provide you with a better personal experience on our websites. The legal basis for the processing of your personal data is your consent pursuant to Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR, which you can give via our cookie banner. Your consent is always voluntary and is not required for the use of the website itself.

3.3.2

Storage period of cookies

Session cookies are deleted after closing the browser. We also use persistent (“permanent”) cookies. Details on the storage period can be found in the cookie management tool.

3.3.3

Individual cookies

For details regarding the individual cookies used, please refer to the “show details” section of our cookie tool. You can find it at any time by clicking on the Cookiebot icon on the left side at the bottom of our website.

3.4

We use a local installation of Matomo on our website. Matomo is an open source analytics tool ([http://www.matomo.org](http://www.matomo.org/)) that enables us to analyze the behavior of visitors in order to offer you a flawless user experience. As we have installed Matomo locally on our web server, no data is transferred to third parties. We use Matomo with an IP masking procedure (i.e. pseudonymization by shortening the IP address) to protect users. We also use cookies for the use of Matomo. Further information on this can be found in our cookie banner. The legal basis for the processing is your consent given via the cookie banner. If you are a registered user, we will also process your data according to section 4.2 below.

4

**Data collection and processing of voluntarily provided data**  

4.1

Contact form or general contact

If you send us enquiries via the contact form or via one of the specified contact options, your message including the contact data you provide there will be stored and processed accordingly for the purpose of processing and answering the enquiry and in the event of follow-up questions. We do not pass this data on to third parties unless this is necessary within the scope of processing and answering your contact enquiry or you have given us your corresponding consent.

If you contact us in the context of an existing contractual relationship or contact us in advance for information about our range of services or our other services, the data and information you provide will be processed for the purpose of processing and answering your contact enquiry in accordance with Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b GDPR (legal basis), and otherwise to safeguard our legitimate interests in accordance with Art. 6 para. 1. Lit. f GDPR for the proper answering of contact enquiries.

The data you enter in the contact form will remain with us until the purpose for storing/processing the data no longer applies and mandatory retention periods (in particular any retention obligations under commercial or tax law) have been fulfilled.

4.2

User Accounts

To make use of personalized services, you will have to register a user account with our websites. During registration we will ask you to provide some personal information, including, but not limited to, your name, valid e-mail address, affiliation, postal address, phone number, password, academic degree, position within your institution or organisation, and your research interests. Also, your IP address will be stored as part of your registration and each time you log into our services. As registered user we will also track your personalized use of the website using Matomo (see section 3.4 above) if you have agreed to the Matomo Cookies, to improve your use of our services. Some of this information is required to properly set up the user account for you to use all of MDPI’s services. MDPI may use this information to fulfil our contract with you (e.g. the publication of your article). Furthermore, MDPI may also use this information internally, e.g., to evaluate and improve our business, respond to any questions, requests or comments you make, or to identify and prevent fraud, claims or other liabilities.

4.3

Newsletters

With your consent, you can subscribe to the newsletters we offer as part of our services (e.g. regarding journals or other offerings).

For the subscription to our newsletters, we use the so-called double-opt-in procedure. This means that after your registration, we will send you an e-mail to the e-mail address you provided, in which we ask you to confirm that you wish to receive the newsletter. In addition, we store your respective IP addresses used and times of registration and confirmation. The purpose of this procedure is to be able to prove your registration and, if necessary, to clarify a possible misuse of your personal data. Only your e-mail address is required for sending the newsletter. The provision of further, separately marked data is voluntary and will be used to address you personally. After your confirmation, we store the data you have provided for the purpose of sending you the newsletter (legal basis is Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR).

You can withdraw your consent to the sending of the newsletter at any time and unsubscribe from the newsletter. You can declare the withdrawal by clicking on the link provided in every newsletter email.

5

**Disclosure to third parties**  

5.1

We pass on at least some of your data that we collect in accordance with the aforementioned paragraphs to processors. These process your data only on our instructions and not for their own purposes (Art. 28, 19, GDPR). These are companies that can be assigned to the following categories:

5.2

Third party tools, websites, and providers of tools or services engaged by MDPI to support submission checks and processing, peer-review, the editorial process, integrity investigations and/or scientific communication

5.3

Third party online databases, or platforms or indexing & abstracting services to share article data as published on mdpi.com

5.4

Affiliates of MDPI to fulfill MDPI’s services and contractual obligations

5.5

If you are associated with a university, institution, or society that has entered into an agreement with MDPI, your personal data like name and email address may be disclosed or shared in accordance with the terms and purposes stipulated in that agreement.

5.6

If we transfer data to recipients in a third country (located outside the European Economic Area, “EEA”), we will only do so if there is an adequate data protection level in accordance with Art. 44 - 50 GDPR. Some third countries are certified by the European Commission through so-called adequacy decisions as having a data protection standard that is comparable to the level in the European Economic Area. You can find a list of these countries at [https://commission.europa.eu/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/adequacy-decisions\_en](https://commission.europa.eu/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/adequacy-decisions_en). If a country does not have a comparable data protection standard, we ensure that data protection is sufficiently guaranteed by other measures. This is possible, for example, through binding corporate rules, standard contractual clauses of the European Commission for the protection of personal data, certificates or recognised codes of conduct. Otherwise, we do not transfer your personal data to countries outside the EU or the EEA or to international organisations, unless expressly stated otherwise in this privacy policy.

6

**Duration of storage**  

Unless otherwise stated, we initially process and store your personal data for the duration for which the respective purpose of use requires storage. If applicable, this also includes the periods of the initiation of a contract and the processing of a contract. On this basis, personal data is regularly deleted within the period required for the fulfilment of our contractual and/or legal obligations, unless its further processing for a limited period is necessary for the following purposes:

* Fulfilment of legal storage obligations (in particular due to commercial or tax law)
* Preservation of evidence, taking into account the statute of limitations.

7

**Your rights**  

You have the following rights in relation to personal data relating to you:

* Right to access,
* Right to rectification or erasure,
* Right to restriction of processing,
* Right to object to processing,
* Right to data portability.

Please send your written request to MDPI AG, Grosspeteranlage 5, 4052 Basel, Switzerland or to the e-mail address: [\[email protected\]](https://www.mdpi.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

You also have the right to complain to a data protection supervisory authority about our processing of your personal data.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 17 December 2024.

### Further Information

### Guidelines

### MDPI Initiatives

### Follow MDPI

Subscribe to receive issue release notifications and newsletters from MDPI journals

Acoustics Acta Microbiologica Hellenica Actuators Administrative Sciences Adolescents Advances in Respiratory Medicine Aerobiology Aerospace Agriculture AgriEngineering Agrochemicals Agronomy AI Air Algorithms Allergies Alloys Analytica Analytics Anatomia Anesthesia Research Animals Antibiotics Antibodies Antioxidants Applied Biosciences Applied Mechanics Applied Microbiology Applied Nano Applied Sciences Applied System Innovation AppliedChem AppliedMath Aquaculture Journal Architecture Arthropoda Arts Astronomy Atmosphere Atoms Audiology Research Automation Axioms Bacteria Batteries Behavioral Sciences Beverages Big Data and Cognitive Computing BioChem Bioengineering Biologics Biology Biology and Life Sciences Forum Biomass Biomechanics BioMed Biomedicines BioMedInformatics Biomimetics Biomolecules Biophysica Biosensors BioTech Birds Blockchains Brain Sciences Buildings Businesses C Cancers Cardiogenetics Catalysts Cells Ceramics Challenges ChemEngineering Chemistry Chemistry Proceedings Chemosensors Children Chips CivilEng Clean Technologies Climate Clinical and Translational Neuroscience Clinical Bioenergetics Clinics and Practice Clocks & Sleep Coasts Coatings Colloids and Interfaces Colorants Commodities Complications Compounds Computation Computer Sciences & Mathematics Forum Computers Condensed Matter Conservation Construction Materials Corrosion and Materials Degradation Cosmetics COVID Crops Cryo Cryptography Crystals Current Issues in Molecular Biology Current Oncology Dairy Data Dentistry Journal Dermato Dermatopathology Designs Diabetology Diagnostics Dietetics Digital Disabilities Diseases Diversity DNA Drones Drugs and Drug Candidates Dynamics Earth Ecologies Econometrics Economies Education Sciences Electricity Electrochem Electronic Materials Electronics Emergency Care and Medicine Encyclopedia Endocrines Energies Energy Storage and Applications Eng Engineering Proceedings Entropy Environmental and Earth Sciences Proceedings Environments Epidemiologia Epigenomes European Burn Journal European Journal of Investigation in Health, Psychology and Education Fermentation Fibers FinTech Fire Fishes Fluids Foods Forecasting Forensic Sciences Forests Fossil Studies Foundations Fractal and Fractional Fuels Future Future Internet Future Pharmacology Future Transportation Galaxies Games Gases Gastroenterology Insights Gastrointestinal Disorders Gastronomy Gels Genealogy Genes Geographies GeoHazards Geomatics Geometry Geosciences Geotechnics Geriatrics Glacies Gout, Urate, and Crystal Deposition Disease Grasses Hardware Healthcare Hearts Hemato Hematology Reports Heritage Histories Horticulturae Hospitals Humanities Humans Hydrobiology Hydrogen Hydrology Hygiene Immuno Infectious Disease Reports Informatics Information Infrastructures Inorganics Insects Instruments Intelligent Infrastructure and Construction International Journal of Environmental Research and Public Health International Journal of Financial Studies International Journal of Molecular Sciences International Journal of Neonatal Screening International Journal of Plant Biology International Journal of Topology International Journal of Translational Medicine International Journal of Turbomachinery, Propulsion and Power International Medical Education Inventions IoT ISPRS International Journal of Geo-Information J Journal of Ageing and Longevity Journal of Cardiovascular Development and Disease Journal of Clinical & Translational Ophthalmology Journal of Clinical Medicine Journal of Composites Science Journal of Cybersecurity and Privacy Journal of Dementia and Alzheimer's Disease Journal of Developmental Biology Journal of Experimental and Theoretical Analyses Journal of Functional Biomaterials Journal of Functional Morphology and Kinesiology Journal of Fungi Journal of Imaging Journal of Intelligence Journal of Low Power Electronics and Applications Journal of Manufacturing and Materials Processing Journal of Marine Science and Engineering Journal of Market Access & Health Policy Journal of Molecular Pathology Journal of Nanotheranostics Journal of Nuclear Engineering Journal of Otorhinolaryngology, Hearing and Balance Medicine Journal of Parks Journal of Personalized Medicine Journal of Pharmaceutical and BioTech Industry Journal of Respiration Journal of Risk and Financial Management Journal of Sensor and Actuator Networks Journal of the Oman Medical Association Journal of Theoretical and Applied Electronic Commerce Research Journal of Vascular Diseases Journal of Xenobiotics Journal of Zoological and Botanical Gardens Journalism and Media Kidney and Dialysis Kinases and Phosphatases Knowledge LabMed Laboratories Land Languages Laws Life Limnological Review Lipidology Liquids Literature Livers Logics Logistics Lubricants Lymphatics Machine Learning and Knowledge Extraction Machines Macromol Magnetism Magnetochemistry Marine Drugs Materials Materials Proceedings Mathematical and Computational Applications Mathematics Medical Sciences Medical Sciences Forum Medicina Medicines Membranes Merits Metabolites Metals Meteorology Methane Methods and Protocols Metrics Metrology Micro Microbiology Research Micromachines Microorganisms Microplastics Minerals Mining Modelling Modern Mathematical Physics Molbank Molecules Multimodal Technologies and Interaction Muscles Nanoenergy Advances Nanomanufacturing Nanomaterials NDT Network Neuroglia Neurology International NeuroSci Nitrogen Non-Coding RNA Nursing Reports Nutraceuticals Nutrients Obesities Oceans Onco Optics Oral Organics Organoids Osteology Oxygen Parasitologia Particles Pathogens Pathophysiology Pediatric Reports Pets Pharmaceuticals Pharmaceutics Pharmacoepidemiology Pharmacy Philosophies Photochem Photonics Phycology Physchem Physical Sciences Forum Physics Physiologia Plants Plasma Platforms Pollutants Polymers Polysaccharides Populations Poultry Powders Proceedings Processes Prosthesis Proteomes Psychiatry International Psychoactives Psychology International Publications Quantum Beam Science Quantum Reports Quaternary Radiation Reactions Real Estate Receptors Recycling Regional Science and Environmental Economics Religions Remote Sensing Reports Reproductive Medicine Resources Rheumato Risks Robotics Ruminants Safety Sci Scientia Pharmaceutica Sclerosis Seeds Sensors Separations Sexes Signals Sinusitis Smart Cities Social Sciences Société Internationale d’Urologie Journal Societies Software Soil Systems Solar Solids Spectroscopy Journal Sports Standards Stats Stresses Surfaces Surgeries Surgical Techniques Development Sustainability Sustainable Chemistry Symmetry SynBio Systems Targets Taxonomy Technologies Telecom Textiles Thalassemia Reports Therapeutics Thermo Time and Space Tomography Tourism and Hospitality Toxics Toxins Transplantology Trauma Care Trends in Higher Education Tropical Medicine and Infectious Disease Universe Urban Science Uro Vaccines Vehicles Venereology Veterinary Sciences Vibration Virtual Worlds Viruses Vision Waste Water Wild Wind Women World World Electric Vehicle Journal Youth Zoonotic Diseases  Subscribe

© 1996-2024 MDPI (Basel, Switzerland) unless otherwise stated

Disclaimer

Disclaimer/Publisher’s Note: The statements, opinions and data contained in all publications are solely those of the individual author(s) and contributor(s) and not of MDPI and/or the editor(s). MDPI and/or the editor(s) disclaim responsibility for any injury to people or property resulting from any ideas, methods, instructions or products referred to in the content.

We use cookies on our website to ensure you get the best experience.  
Read more about our cookies [here](https://www.mdpi.com/about/privacy).

Share Link
----------

[\[email protected\]](https://www.mdpi.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)[](https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=&hashtags=&url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mdpi.com%2Fabout%2Fprivacy&via=MDPIOpenAccess "Twitter")[](http://www.linkedin.com/shareArticle?mini=true&url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mdpi.com%2Fabout%2Fprivacy&title=%26source%3Dhttps%3A%2F%2Fwww.mdpi.com "LinkedIn")[](https://www.facebook.com/sharer.php?u=https://www.mdpi.com/about/privacy "facebook")[](javascript:void(0); "Wechat")[](http://www.reddit.com/submit?url=https://www.mdpi.com/about/privacy "Reddit")[](http://www.mendeley.com/import/?url=https://www.mdpi.com/about/privacy "Mendeley")[](http://www.citeulike.org/posturl?url=https://www.mdpi.com/about/privacy "CiteULike")

Copy

_clear_

Share
-----

https://www.mdpi.com/about/privacy

_clear_
